[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Dana any movement really since I spoke to you yesterday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "The only movement is that the President of the United States and the four congressional leaders two in each party sat down and faced each other eyeball-to- eyeball and they did talked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Are the Republicans making any headwind with their argument that he is also to blame here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "In Washington, not so much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Why don't the Republicans causing on this mess work harder and quicker to resolve it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNPS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Listen we've worked all day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP", "House"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "I mean do you see any way that the president can negotiate down from his current position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, I think very hard because this is really an internal GOP fight in the House.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "But I can hear you both now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "``", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "For arguments sake he's John Boehner, what would your pitch be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "My pitch could be this \"Look, you wouldn't want us doing this if it was Republican President.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "So what is your sensible coherent argument for why that is not an acceptable position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, listen, history is littered with bad laws that once in a fact and later were changed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What was going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Look what you see, good as a harbor, there's the Statue of Liberty they got to -- they got it perked up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["July 4th"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Morgan"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "What is it mean, like for you on the sharp end financially hearing this shutdown?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Well, it's just as outrageous for us, Mr. Morgan, coming on the heels of eight months of closure after Sandy only to reopen the Statue of Liberty on July 4th.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "And unlike people who get furloughed who work for the government and so on, you have no hope of getting any of that money back it's a right-off, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "There's no recovery of our revenues, there's no recovery on the employees lost wages.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "What is your personal view about the Statue of Liberty being closed for business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I mean, as an American and as someone who has worked around the Statue for almost 30 years, it's outrageous, it's illogical.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "This is no right way to run a business, is it Jack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "It's terrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "But why are they not talking all the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "It took him 18 months to call the Head of the Senate after getting elected.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Does the president have a good point that you think here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "What the country needs is a growing, thriving medical business and we're cashing it for entrepreneurs and we're taxing revenues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Here's the point there, Jack.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "If you had to renegade, when you are running G.E. and you are the boss, you are the John Boehner figure if you like of the Republican Party and suddenly you got a Ted Cruz, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "I thought I was going to be on marketing guide on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["G.E."], "PERSON": ["John Boehner", "Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "But if you had to take Cruz and suddenly burst out of nowhere and begin to run your gig for you and call on a (inaudible) what would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I wouldn't be dealing with him alone, but I'll be listening to him to see what he had to say and I'll be trying to figure out if he made any sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "How do you try and change the way Washington has now become?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Piers, I've read a column today from Linkedn, a lot of action.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "How do you feel about you've been sent home, no pay, and you may or may not end up getting paid for this period?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "I feel awful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "How do you feel about all the -- how do you feel about all the members of congress getting their salaries in this period?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "I don't think they should receive any pay.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "What have you said to her about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, it's kind of difficult to explain to a five-year old that mommy is not working.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "You still pretty pleased of your self that the Republicans have lead the government into a meltdown, shutdowns affecting so many normal lives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "You know, it's funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "TO", "VB", ":", "NN", ":", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Can I ask you a question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "... to deserve (ph) GDP over the next 10 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "When was the last time a federal budget was passed and signed into law by Barack Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "It doesn't matter.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 366, "question": "When was the last time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "(Inaudible) The government spend money...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "When was the last time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "The government spends money for appropriations bills like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NIH"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "As you are a former CIA spy, this is your wheelhouse, what do you think or what do have to say there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Like every other American I'm absolutely appalled that no advancement has been made and that the children in NIH are being turned away and all the terrible consequences that you saw earlier at the top of the segment, furloughing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "And at the moment, is the situation -- this kind of trial is on hold to the duration of the shutdown?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "I think Brian can answer that better.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Healthcare"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "How do you feel about the fact that squabbling politicians in Washington might -- and I say might at this stage -- has some effect on your chances of survival?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "MD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I think it's pretty ridiculous that -- especially since the whole debates over Healthcare Law like they're trying to engulf all of these.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Children's Cancer Research Hospital"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Surely -- whichever side of this argument you're on, it is time to get this sorted, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Well, and I think, look, my wife worked for seven years in the Children's Cancer Research Hospital and when you see these parents that are told that their kids' scans don't go well, it is the entire world they're in crumbling around them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "What do you think of the poisonous atmosphere in Washington right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Well, actually I was a subject of partisan attacks.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "You're prepared to go back and face yet further questioning in this court case, if they ask you, is that your position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "I will be back when the trial gets into the court.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "They simply don't want to believe the version of events that you and Amanda have put forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "OLLECITO: No -- well, it's not the justice in my -- a version of defense or Amanda, the version of defense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "I mean, do you with hindsight that you'd never laid eyes on her that you had never become embroiled in such a lurid crime scandal as this become?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "POS", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "What do you know about that knife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Well basically, in my opinion just logically, it's ridiculous that's anybody will bring such a big knife from my house to another house.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "What is your message to Meredith Kercher's family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Basically, I feel a lot of compassion for their situation and it's horrible because the -- her, their daughter is no more in this world.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Meredith Kercher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["October of 2008"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Morgan", "Meredith Kercher", "Rudy Guede"]}, "docId": "131002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "NNP", "IN", "CD", ",", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Why do you feel so strongly with your exemplary legal background that she is 100 percent innocent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Mr. Morgan, five years ago, October of 2008, less than a year after the murder of Meredith Kercher, Rudy Guede, overwhelming evidence.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}]